eclipse.org 2019-12-20

# Eclipse Foundation Website Privacy Policy | The Eclipse Foundation

May 24, 2018

The Eclipse Foundation, Inc. ("Eclipse Foundation", "Us" or "We") is a member-supported not-for-profit foundation which acts as the steward of our open source projects, community, and ecosystem. We are committed to our community members’ rights to privacy. We promise to share transparently all aspects of how Eclipse Foundation projects and websites work in regards to privacy, terms, and personal data, and We are in full support of efforts to ensure your protection online. We only collect your personal data with your consent, and collect only as much as We need to provide you the service you request. For example, We need your personal data to register you to one of our conferences. Each time We collect additional personal data from you We will explain what We collect, why We need it, how We use it, how long We keep it, and how We protect it. 

You can withdraw consent anytime. We will respect your wishes.

## Personal Information on Eclipse Foundation Websites

As a platform for open source innovation and collaboration, personal information on all Eclipse Foundation websites is either meant to be shared, for example records of your contributions to our open source projects, or protected, such as your name and email address when you subscribe to our newsletter. 

Any personal data you share with Us, We protect according to this Privacy policy.

## Individual Access to Personal Information

We will respond within 30 days to your requests to have access to your personal information collected by Us. We will promptly correct inaccuracies, as the case may be, and We will delete it and/or anonymize it upon your request. Please contact [privacy@eclipse.org](mailto:privacy@eclipse.org) to make such a request. 

## Information Security and Quality

We protect the integrity of your personal information with appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption for transmission of certain forms of information, to help keep it secure, accurate, current, and complete. 

Your personal information may be stored in Canada, the European Union and the United States, always with our same high security standards. 

One of the primary purposes of the Eclipse Foundation and its websites is to enable collaborative open source software development. Doing so necessarily requires Us to maintain records of authorship related to all contributions. Any personally identifiable information collected by virtue of your contributions will be publicly available on the Internet in unencrypted form and without access restriction. 

We also offer services to our community which provide the ability for users of Eclipse software to store data on Eclipse Foundation servers through services including, but not limited to, the User Storage Service and the Automated Error Reporting Initiative. Any data stored through these services will be publicly available on the Internet in unencrypted form and without access restriction. Therefore, you should not use these services to store passwords, any personally identifiable information, any confidential business information, or anything else that you do not want to be generally and publicly available. 

## Clickstream Data and Cookies

We sometimes collect anonymous information from visits and contributions to Eclipse Foundation websites to help provide better service. For example, We keep track of the domains from which people visit and We also measure visitor activity on Eclipse Foundation websites, but in ways that keep the information anonymous. This anonymous information is sometimes known as "clickstream data." We may use and aggregate this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help Us tailor our websites to better serve Eclipse participants. 

Some Eclipse Foundation website pages use cookies to better serve you when you return to the site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of our sites may not function properly. 

Our sites may also set a session cookie to enable them to function properly. In such cases, the session cookie will only last for the length of your session, and the only information recorded will be that which is necessary to enable the website to function properly, and no personally identifiable information will be recorded in the session cookie. 

## Business Relationships

This website contains links to other website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such website. 

## Notification of Changes

This privacy statement was last updated on May 24, 2018. A notice will be posted on this website home page for thirty (30) days whenever this privacy statement is changed. 

## Questions Regarding This Policy

Questions regarding this Privacy policy should be directed to: [privacy@eclipse.org](mailto:privacy@eclipse.org).
